

GOLAM ISHTIYAQE

FULL-STACK WEB APP DEVELOPER | REACT, DJANGO, PYTHON

CONTACT

Phone

01863455599

Whatsapp

01749794512

Email

gishtiyatiqe033@gmail.com

Address

2/H/6 ka, golden street, ring road, shyamoli, Dhaka

EXPERTISE

- React, Tailwind-CSS, html, CSS for Front-end.
- Django, Python for Backend.
- Full stack development
- Browser Automation
- web Scraping (Playwright, Beautiful-soup, Selenium, etc)
- Data Science
- Machine learning

(Model Training, Model Building, Model Deployment etc)

• Al integration like

(GPT-3, GPT-4, claude, etc)

- Website security.
- Server management and deployment

(VPS, Nginx, Apache, etc)

ABOUT ME

As an expert in front-end and back-end development, I build high-performance web apps with React, Django, and more. I offer responsive, SEO-friendly design, fast load times, and optimized media handling, specializing in e-commerce, web scraping, and AI solutions.

EDUCATION

• B.S.C in C.S.E 2024-Running

Bangladesh University of Business and Technology (BUBT)

- Diploma in Computer Engineering 2020-2024
 Daffodil Technical Institute (DTI)
- H.S.C in Business Study 2016-2018

Mohammadpur Preparatory School and College

• S.S.C in Business Study 2006-2015

Noakhali Zilla School

EXPERIENCE

• Fiverr Since 2023

Full Stack Web App Developer

- *Upwork Since 2024*Full Stack Web App Developer
- WebCarib.xyz 2023-2024 Full Stack Developer
- Alibaba24bd.com 2022-2023 Full Stack Developer
- SodeshBuy.com 2020-2022 Administration and Clients handling
- *Ecargo.com.bd* 2022-2023 Full Stack Developer

CLIENTS REVIEW









REFERENCE

• Abdullah Al Faruque

Advocate (G.P.), Bangladesh Bar Council District Judge Court, Noakhali. 01712091426